Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Time rushes by, seasons change, autumn winds bring melancholy♪
♪يمر الوقت بسرعة، وتتغير الفصول، وتجلب رياح الخريف الكآبة♪
♪Scattered fragments can't piece together the memories of the past♪
♪الشظايا المتناثرة لا يمكنها تجميع ذكريات الماضي♪
♪The movie hasn't ended, tears glimmer in my eyes♪
♪الفيلم لم ينتهي بعد، والدموع تتلألأ في عيني♪
♪Sitting alone by the street, feeling lost and hesitant♪
♪أجلس وحدي في الشارع، أشعر بالضياع والتردد♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it drift, let it dance♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تنجرف، دعها ترقص♪
♪Whispering softly♪
♪همس بهدوء♪
♪The flowers that withered in my hand♪
♪الزهور التي ذبلت في يدي♪
♪Cannot call back the ones gone♪
♪لا أستطيع استدعاء من رحلوا♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it shatter, let it fade away♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تتحطم، دعها تتلاشى♪
♪Old stories like drifting dust♪
♪قصص قديمة مثل الغبار المنجرف♪
♪Letters too short for my long feelings, youth slips away♪
♪رسائل قصيرة جدًا بالنسبة لمشاعري الطويلة، الشباب يتلاشى♪
♪Farewell, my dear♪
♪ وداعا يا عزيزي ♪
♪Endless pain through day and night cycles♪
♪ألم لا ينتهي خلال دورات الليل والنهار♪
♪Longing and care♪
♪الشوق والرعاية♪
=Life Like=
=مثل الحياة=
=Episode 9=
=الحلقة 9=
A bicycle?
دراجة هوائية؟
What?
ماذا؟
Not good enough for you?
ليس جيدا بما فيه الكفاية بالنسبة لك؟
I am the star of Night Shanghai,
أنا نجم ليلة شنغهاي،
and you're making me sitting on a bicycle?
وأنت تجعلني أجلس على دراجة؟
Don't be dramatic.
لا تكن دراميًا.
Get on,
إستمر
my star.
نجمتي.
♪Chimes echo through the alleys worn by time♪
♪تتردد الأجراس في الأزقة التي تآكلها الزمن♪
♪Flickering fireflies surround your deep face♪
♪ اليراعات المتلألئة تحيط بوجهك العميق ♪
♪I hold fresh flowers, you hum softly♪
♪أحمل الزهور الطازجة، أنت تدندن بهدوء♪
♪Melodious dance steps, love ripples♪
♪خطوات رقص لحنية، تموجات الحب♪
♪Time rushes by, seasons change, autumn winds bring melancholy♪
♪يمر الوقت بسرعة، وتتغير الفصول، وتجلب رياح الخريف الكآبة♪
♪Scattered fragments can't piece together the memories of the past♪
♪الشظايا المتناثرة لا يمكنها تجميع ذكريات الماضي♪
♪The movie hasn't ended, tears glimmer in my eyes♪
♪الفيلم لم ينتهي بعد، والدموع تتلألأ في عيني♪
♪Sitting alone by the street, feeling lost and hesitant♪
♪أجلس وحدي في الشارع، أشعر بالضياع والتردد♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it drift, let it dance♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تنجرف، دعها ترقص♪
♪Whispering softly♪
♪همس بهدوء♪
♪The flowers that withered in my hand♪
♪الزهور التي ذبلت في يدي♪
Slow down.
ابطئ.
Yes,
نعم،
my star.
نجمتي.
♪Old stories like drifting dust♪
♪قصص قديمة مثل الغبار المنجرف♪
♪Letters too short for my long feelings, youth slips away♪
♪رسائل قصيرة جدًا بالنسبة لمشاعري الطويلة، الشباب يتلاشى♪
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Here.
هنا.
I'll get us a better ride next time.
سأحصل لنا على رحلة أفضل في المرة القادمة.
You ride like a maniac!
أنت تركب مثل المجنون!
Hey…
يا…
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I won't let it happen again.
لن أسمح بحدوث ذلك مرة أخرى.
Since you apologized nicely,
بما أنك اعتذرت بشكل لطيف،
here, take a coin.
هنا، خذ قطعة نقدية.
Hey…
يا…
That's all the great Night Shanghai star's
هذا كل ما يتعلق بنجم ليلة شنغهاي العظيم
giving me?
تعطيني؟
Take it or leave it.
خذها أو اتركها.
I'll take it.
أنا أعتبر.
We're here.
نحن هنا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Boss, about the medicine shipment for Yamamoto…
يا رئيس، بخصوص شحنة الدواء إلى ياماموتو…
I'll give him a call tonight.
سأتصل به الليلة.
We'll coordinate then.
سوف نقوم بالتنسيق بعد ذلك.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Are you scared?
هل انت خائفة؟
No.
لا.
A bug flew into my eye.
طار حشرة في عيني.
Better?
أحسن؟
Mm.
مم.
Oh?
أوه؟
You're here, Musheng.
أنت هنا، موشينج.
Yue.
يوي.
Yao.
لهم.
Chairman Du.
الرئيس دو.
Captain Luo.
الكابتن لوه.
Well, well,
حسنا حسنا
Musheng sure has a way with women.
من المؤكد أن موشينغ لديه طريقة مع النساء.
Won over Ms. Rose herself.
فازت بالسيدة روز بنفسها.
All thanks to you, Yao,
كل الشكر لك يا ياو
for arranging our meeting.
لترتيب اجتماعنا.
If it isn't the star of Night Shanghai.
إذا لم يكن نجم ليلة شنغهاي.
The Rose in daylight is even more captivating than at night.
الوردة في ضوء النهار أكثر جاذبية من الوردة في الليل.
Thanks for the compliment, Captain Luo.
شكرا على الثناء، كابتن لوه.
Let's start the feast.
لنبدأ العيد.
The wine's here!
النبيذ هنا!
Come on.
تعال.
Pour one out for the Boss.
صب واحدة للرئيس.
Here.
هنا.
Why is she everywhere?
لماذا هي في كل مكان؟
Ms. Rose is Musheng's friend.
السيدة روز هي صديقة موشينغ.
Friend,
صديقي
not wife.
ليست زوجة.
Well, well.
حسنا حسنا.
Who's upset the princess
من أزعج الأميرة؟
of the North City Chamber of Commerce?
غرفة تجارة مدينة الشمال؟
Ms. Man Li's upset.
السيدة مان لي منزعجة.
This should be fun to watch.
يجب أن يكون من الممتع مشاهدته.
Shut your trap.
أغلق فمك.
Here.
هنا.
Musheng,
موشينج،
this first drink's for you.
هذا المشروب الأول لك.
You saved my life.
لقد انقذت حياتي.
Yue,
يوي،
don't say that.
لا تقل ذلك
You're making me embarrassed.
أنت تجعلني أشعر بالحرج.
Chairman Du,
الرئيس دو،
let me toast you.
دعني أشرب نخبًا لك.
Thank you for looking after Musheng.
شكرا لك على رعايتك لموشينغ.
Drink slowly.
اشرب ببطء.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Some women can be so spoiled.
يمكن لبعض النساء أن تكون مدللة للغاية.
Rose,
وَردَة،
here.
هنا.
A toast to you.
نخب لك.
I'm glad you came.
أنا سعيد أنك  جئت.
Ms. Rose.
السيدة روز.
Let me give you a toast.
دعني أعطيك نخبًا.
Oh, dear.
يا عزيزي.
Rose,
وَردَة،
your dress is soaked.
فستانك مبلل.
Maybe
ربما
you should take care of that?
هل يجب عليك الاهتمام بهذا؟
I'll go freshen up.
سأذهب لتجديد نشاطي.
I'm sure
انا متأكد
you didn't mean
لم تقصد
to spill.
لعبتين.
You…
أنت…
Give me a hand!
أعطني يد المساعدة!
Let's carry on.
دعونا نستمر.
- Cheers!
- هتاف!
Bottoms up!
من الأسفل إلى الأعلى!
No one's leaving till we're all drunk.
لن يغادر أحد حتى نكون جميعًا في حالة سُكر.
Keep going.
يستمر في التقدم.
Come on.
تعال.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
We haven't decided the winner yet, right?
لم نقرر الفائز بعد، أليس كذلك؟
I'm afraid of you?
انا خائفة منك؟
Go on!
إستمر!
Yao, play him!
ياو، العب معه!
Come on.
تعال.
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
Drink!
شرب!
See?
يرى؟
You lost.
لقد خسرت.
Musheng's got skills.
موشينغ لديه مهارات.
Luo Zhenyao can't keep up.
لوه تشن ياو لا يستطيع المواكبة.
Idiot.
غبي.
You sure you got this?
هل أنت متأكد أنك حصلت على هذا؟
Get up, you.
انهض انت.
Six.
ستة.
Five!
خمسة!
Musheng lost.
لقد خسر موشنغ.
Come on. Drink!
هيا، اشرب!
You're not any better, Musheng.
أنت لست أفضل، موشينغ.
Chairman Du.
الرئيس دو.
Ms. Rose.
السيدة روز.
Ms. Rose, Musheng's had too much to drink.
السيدة روز، لقد شرب موشينغ الكثير من الشراب.
You should stay
يجب عليك البقاء
and take care of him tonight.
واعتني به الليلة.
Of course.
بالطبع.
You really
انت حقا
don't miss a chance
لا تفوت الفرصة
to charm everyone, do you?
لتسحر الجميع، أليس كذلك؟
You guys stay too.
أنتم أيضا ابقوا.
Play some mahjong.
العب بعض لعبة الماهجونغ.
Loosen up a little.
استرخي قليلا.
Musheng.
موشينج.
Time to play some mahjong…
حان الوقت للعب بعض الماهجونغ…
Come on. Hurry up!
هيا، أسرع!
Everything's ready.
كل شئ جاهز .
Come on. Let's play some mahjong.
هيا، لنلعب لعبة الماهجونغ.
Let's play mahjong.
دعونا نلعب الماهجونغ.
We've been waiting for everyone to gather for a game.
لقد كنا ننتظر الجميع للتجمع للعبة.
I'll help you.
سأساعدك.
(I may as well)
(أنا أيضا قد)
(take this opportunity to look for clues.)
(اغتنم هذه الفرصة للبحث عن الأدلة.)
♪The world all marvels as fireworks rise♪
♪يندهش العالم كله عندما ترتفع الألعاب النارية♪
♪Magnificent like a blooming dream♪
♪رائعة مثل حلم مزدهر♪
♪Yet who sees the lingering red after the burst♪
♪ومع ذلك من يرى اللون الأحمر المتبقي بعد الانفجار♪
♪Fading into the cold night sky♪
♪تتلاشى في سماء الليل الباردة♪
♪Without the graves of blood and fire♪
♪بدون قبور الدم والنار♪
♪How could there be glory in prosperous times♪
♪كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك مجد في الأوقات المزدهرة♪
♪May that fleeting red of fireworks remain in our hearts♪
♪أتمنى أن يبقى ذلك اللون الأحمر العابر للألعاب النارية في قلوبنا♪
♪Freedom and faith engraved forever♪
♪الحرية والإيمان محفوران إلى الأبد♪
♪You and I are both in the muddy flood♪
♪أنت وأنا في الطوفان الموحل♪
♪Destined to share life and death together♪
♪مُقدَّر لنا أن نتقاسم الحياة والموت معًا♪
♪Life lights the night sky like fireworks' red♪
♪الحياة تضيء سماء الليل مثل الألعاب النارية الحمراء♪
♪Not seeking to engulf the world, just refusing mediocrity♪
♪لا أسعى إلى ابتلاع العالم، فقط أرفض الرداءة♪
♪Even if a single second is all we have in life♪
♪حتى لو كانت ثانية واحدة هي كل ما لدينا في الحياة♪
♪We must sow seeds for our ideals♪
♪علينا أن نزرع بذورًا لمُثُلنا العليا♪